Guide to the Medical Center records, 1825-2005 RG0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Women's board, 1898-1993; RG0007 Series 14; 6 Linear feet
  - Women's Board receipts & bank statements, 1953-1959 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - First Photo, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Gift shop planning sessions, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Women's Board historic memorabilia includes, photos & programs, 1962-1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Inventory, correspondence, Friday Report, news release, 1958-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - List of names & home addresses, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Newsweek, correspondence, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Membership applications of resignations or previously deceased members, 1955-1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bound minutes Book, 1927-1930 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Women's Board meeting minutes, 01/1951 -06/1954 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Women's Board meeting minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bound minutes book, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Women's Board meeting minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Minutes & correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Executive committee minutes, (large binder), 1978-1981 Executive committee minutes, (large binder), 1981-1984 Women's board reference file to minutes, (large binder), 1969-1982
  - Miscellaneous reference materials, 1966-1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1968-1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous files, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - President's notebook, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Agenda, executive minutes, finance, correspondence, finance, reports, correspondence, & miscellaneous papers; large binder
  - President's notebook, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Various minutes, shop reports, new shop plans, treasurer, First Foto, correspondence, & annual reports; large binder
  - President's notebook, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Meeting notices, agendas, executive committee minutes, Board meeting minutes, gift shop, treasure's reports, finance committee, program information, annual reports, By-Laws committee, & miscellaneous correspondence, large binder
  - President's notebook, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Meeting notices, agendas, executive committee minutes, Board meeting minutes, gift shop, finance committee, First Foto, Program information, correspondence, bazaar, annual reports, patient care committee, & By-Laws, large binder
  - President's notebook, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Meeting notices, agendas, executive committee minutes, Board meeting Minutes, gift shop reports, ad hoc committee on personnel, finance committee reports, First Foto, program committee, correspondence w/hospital officials, patient care committee, annual reports, general correspondence, & W.B. memorial silver, large binder
  - President's notebook, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Meeting notices, agendas, endowment fund correspondence, finance committee, executive minutes, Treasurer's reports, First Foto, Dral history project, annual reports, general correspondence, correspondence w/hospital & University officials, large binder
  - President's notebook, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notices, Board minutes, executive minutes, letters, financial statements, First Foto, correspondence w/hospital officials, gift shop, & annual reports, large binder
  - President's notebook, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Audit, notices, board minutes, Treasurer's reports, First Foto, letters, & correspondence, large binder
  - Obituary, news release, & information on Elizabeth W. Wilson, 1978-1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Women's Board papers, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Proposals G.S., 04/1995 -05/1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Records, 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook, 1898-1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Loose item, large binder
  - Recommendations for membership to the Board, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Presbyterian Medical Center calendar, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Loose item
  - Women's Board stationary w/envelopes, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Gavel, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Loose item, artifact
  - Card catalogue of Board members, circa 1950-circa 1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Contents of little box within Box 4
  - Directory, 1898 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Contents of little box within Box 4, note: original & first copy
  - Directory, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Directory, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Directory, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Contents of little box within Box 4, 2 copies
  - Directory, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Directory, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Directory, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Directory, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Contents of little box within Box 4, 5 copies
  - Directory supplement, 11/1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Contents of little box within Box 4, 4 copies
  - Pamphlet of the Women's Board titled, Abbreviated History & Synopsis of Activities, 02/1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Alumni Association for Health Services Management and Policy, 1962-1999; RG0007 Series 15; 1 Linear foot (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series consists of correspondence, meeting minutes, history of the alumni association, papers of David Woodrum, and address lists. The materials range in date from 1962-99.
- Health Services Management and Policy Alumni Association, ca.1965-ca.1975; RG0007 Series 16; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of a scrapbook of events and activities of the Alumni Association for Health Services Management and Policy. The materials range in date from ca. 1965-ca.1975.
  formerly ACC#820
- Women's board, 1996-1998; RG0007 Series 17; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of minutes, agendas, correspondence, history, etc., of the hospital Women's Board. The materials range in date from 1996-98.
  - Agendas and Announcements, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondences, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Janet G. Travell, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Finance Comm. and Treasurer's Report, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - History, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes: 1976, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Articles, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Program Committee and Special Projects, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Telephone directories, 1965-1983, 1986, 1998; RG0007 Series 18; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box SHARED Box 3)
  This series consists of telephone directories of the Medical Center, and range in date from 1965-82.
  - Telephone directories, 1965-1983 (Box 1)
  - GWU Medical Center Telephone Directory, 1976-1986; Series 18 (Box SHARED Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Medical Center Communications Directory, 1998; Series 18 (Box SHARED Box 3, Folder 2)
- Publication, ca.1965; RG0007 Series 19; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of a publication draft titled "Design for Medical Education," a development document for the new Medical School building and facilities. The material dates from ca.1965.
- Department of Pharmacology reprints, 1941-1982; RG0007 Series 20; 3 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series consists of reprints of articles appearing in various journals (in bound volumes) from the Department of Pharmacology, they range in date from 1941-82.
- Films, ca.1970; RG0007 Series 21; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of six miscellaneous 16mm films from the Medical Center. The date range is not discernable, but they are most likely ca.1970.
- School of Public Health and Health Services, 1986-2013; RG0007 Series 22; 2 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4)
  This series consists of organization and accreditation plans, promotional brochures, chartering ceremony documents, photographs, and video tapes. The materials range in date from 1988-2001.
  - Program guides and application packets, 1986-2003 and undated; 15 folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Administrative internship manual, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Program booklet celebrating silver anniversary of class of 1962 Health Administrative Graduates.
  - Negotiating the New Health System: A Nationwide study of Medicaid Managed and Care Contract, 06/1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Student Handbook and Chartering Ceremony, 06/12/1997 -1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Student Handbook (1998-1999) and Chartering Ceremony Program (June 12, 1997).
  - Forty Years of Health Care Administration, 1959-1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Going the Distance for Public Health (video), undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    (Video) "Going the Distance for Public Health" The George Washington University, School of Public Health & Health Services - Graduate Certificate Program
  - GW School of Public Health & Health Services Chartering Ceremony (video parts 1 and 2 of 6), 06/12/1997 (Box 1)
  - 25th Anniversary Celebration of the Class of 1975 of the Health Services Management & Policy Program, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - A Symposium, Reunion, & Roast of Harvey Wertlieb - Program, 10/04/1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Application for Applicant Status - Council on Education for Public Health, 08/24/1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - By George - Special Supplement for the School of Public Health & Health Services (SPPHS), 03/07/2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Center for Health Services Research & Policy - Pamphlet, 04/06/2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence & Memorandums concerning the establishment for a School of Public Health & Health Services, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Council on Education for Public Health Self-Study for Accreditation, 01/1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Doctor of Public Health Degree Program - Proposal, 04/1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Health Law & Policy for Law Students & Lawyers - Program, 1999 ca. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Informational Brochures & Packets on the School of Public Health & Health Services, 1995-2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Initial Accreditation Review of the Master Public Health Program - Report, 02/05/1990 -06/1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Initial Accreditation Review of SPPHS - Report, 06/05/1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Proposed Graduate Degree Programs in Bio-statistics/Epidemiology - Memorandum, 12/15/1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - School Formation Committee on SPHHS - Final Report, 08/01/1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - SPHHS Organization Plan, 09/04/1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - School of Public Health & Health Services - Courses/Programs, 1994-1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Shaping the Future through Education, Community Service, Research with SPHHS - Booklet, 1999 ca. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Faculty Senate Executive Committee on the Establishment of the SPHHS - Report, 03/27/1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: Colloquium & Gibbs Oration, 10/1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Colloquium, 10/1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: COPC Workshop with Hebrew University & National School of Public Health of South Africa, 07/1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Hirch Professor Sara Rosenbam dinner, 10/1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Speech by Surgeon General Satcher with Dean Riegelman-prints & contact sheets, 04/1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: SPHHS Ceremony, 06/12/1997; 2 folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 6, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: SPHHS Colloquium, 06/1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: SPHHS Dinner Ceremony, 06/12/1997; 2 folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 2, Folder 3)
  - Album of photos, etc., 06/12/1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Chartering Ceremony - School of Public Health and Health Services - Dorothy Betts Marvin Theater
  - 10th Anniversary Reception, 2007; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Women's Board, 1907-1927; RG0007 Series 23; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of a bound volume of meeting minutes from the Women's Board of the GW hospital, and dates from May 1907-February 1927.
- Photographs, papers, and videotapes, 1971-2002; RG0007 Series 24; 5 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 2, Oversize BOX 0, Box 1)
  This series consists of photographs, videotapes, audio cassettes, brochures, alumni bulletins, alumni reunion class notes of memories, alumni directories for Health Services Management and Policy, by-laws of School of Public Health and Health Services, and material relatied to the Dr. George Mandel endowment (pharmacology program). The materials range in date from 1971-2002.
  - Alumni Association Luncheon at D.C. Medical Society, 09/15/1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    With negatives
  - Alumni Student Sponsorship Mexican Fiesta, 08/19/1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    All contact sheets
  - Alumni Weekend from 05/1977, GW Giving Newsletter from 03/1991, 05/1977 -03/1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend 1996 and Dinner in honor of H. George Mandel, 10/19/1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Barbeque, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Blades lecture at University Club, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Class dinners, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Computer Sessions, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Convocation, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Dinner for Class of 1949, 09/1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-GW history luncheon, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Reunion Week-Luncheon, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    CD of photos
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Extra Class Photographs, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Freshman Orientation-Opening assembly & alumni lunch, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - GW Follies, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Health Sciences Convocation, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Medical School Alumni & Orientation, Graduation, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - President of Medical Alumni Association, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Resident Matching Program-Class of 1977, 03/14/1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Negatives and contact sheet only
  - Sesquicentennial Convocation, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Sesquicentennial Convocation, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Sophomore Wine and Cheese party & Dr. Clarence Rice, Jr., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Various Class Reunions for GW School of Medicine and Health Sciences, from Class of 1942 to Class of 1987, 10/1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Various Class Reunions for GW School of Medicine and Health Sciences, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Hospital Renovation slides, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 24 medical school slides, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Photo album - Health Sciences Management and Policy Program 40th Anniversary, 10/1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Oversize Item: George Washington University School of Medicine, Class of 1947, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Medical Center Cancer Program-Annual Report, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Grand Rounds Lectures, Frontiers in BioMedicine, GWU Medical Center-advertisement, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - GWU-175th Anniversary Calendar and Homecoming Weekend-pamphlet, 1995-02/10/1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Student Research Day Celebration Medical Center-pamphlet, 01/21/1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous invitations, 1992-1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Directory of Participating Providers health plan, 10/1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tauber Walk Dedication, 10/27/1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Brochures/publications, 1991-2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fred Brown, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - New Hospital Brochures, 2002 ca. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Invitation for opening of new hospital, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - New GW Hospital Technology, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Medical Center Community Outreach programs, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Invitation, program, and news clipping for convocation in honor of President Ronald Reagan, 03/28/1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Ryan Awards papers, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Programs in Health Care administration, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Health Care administration residency roster and meeting minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Health Sciences Administration/Management and Policy Residency rosters, 1983-1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Administrative Residency Manual, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Health Services Management & Policy Program-40th Anniversary Celebration book, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Program for Health Sciences Programs, 05/17/1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bylaws for School of Public Health and Health Sciences, 05/2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - ACEHSA-Site visit team report, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - School of Public Health and Health Services programs, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Program for School of Medicine and Health Sciences Convocation, 04/02/1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Convocation and White Coat Ceremony, 09/24/1999 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    2 copies
  - Program for School of Medicine and Health Sciences Convocation, 09/15/2000 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Diploma Ceremony Pamphlet for graduates of Doctor of Medicine Degree Program, 05/17/1998 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Degrees conferred school of Government & Business Administration including Health Care Administration, 1962-1981 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Bulletin of Alumni Association for Health Care Administration, 1971-1981 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bulletin of Alumni Association for Health Care Administration, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Bulletin for Alumni Association for Health Services Management and Policy, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1952, 40th Reunion booklet, 10/23/1992 -10/24/1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - School of Medicine and Health Sciences, Class of 1956, 40th Class Reunion Directory, 10/17/1996 -10/19/1996 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - School of Medicine and Health Sciences, "H-Street Emeriti" Directory, 10/17/1996 -10/19/1996 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - School of Medicine and Health Sciences, Class of 1989, 10th Class Reunion Directory, 09/23/1999 -09/25/1999 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - School of Medicine and Health Sciences, Class of 1949, 50th Class Reunion Directory, 09/23/1999 -09/25/1999 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Alumni Information, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Report of Treasurer for GWU Alumni Association for Health Care Administration and Minutes, 10/01/1980 -08/31/1981 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - UPDATE Bulletin for Alumni Association for Health Care Administration, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Alumni Association Questionnaire and Alumni Service Awards, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Biographical information of graduates of Pharmacology program at GWU, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Biographical information of graduates of Pharmacology program at GWU, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Biographical information of graduates of Pharmacology program at GWU, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Biographical information of graduates of Pharmacology program at GWU, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - George Mandel, MD-Letters of congratulations on retirement, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - George Mandel, MD-Letters of congratulations on retirement, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - George Mandel dinner-RSVP's, 10/1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - George Mandel-misc., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - George Mandel Endowment, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Including biographical sketch and photos
  - George Mandel brochure, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Loose Items: Paperweight, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Health Services Management and Policy Preceptor
  - Loose Items: Cassette tape, 11/08/1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    AAMC Plenary Session: Leadership Forum
  - Loose Items: Cassette tape, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Frederick H. Gibbs Oration "State Responsibilities, Prerogatives and Perspectives-A Primer" by Mary Jo O'Brien-GWU HSMP Alumni Association; 2 copies
  - Loose Items: Cassette tape, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Frederick H. Gibbs Oration "The Changing Marketplace" by Elliott C. Roberts, Sr.-GWU HSMP Association; 3 copies
  - Loose Items: Cassette tape, 10/22/1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Gibbs Oration by John Zeglis
  - Loose Items: Video tape, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Virtual Reality Surgical Simulation Overview
  - Loose Items: Video tape, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Dr. Claude Moore: The Past is Present
  - Loose Items: Video tape, 02/19/1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    George Washington University Hospital
  - Loose Items: Video tape, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    An interactive meeting with Iris
  - Loose Items: Video tape-no label, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Loose Items: Aerial view of Washington Circle and Campus, 1975 ca. (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Yearbooks, 1948-1992; RG0007 Series 25; 4.5 Linear Feet
  This series consists of Medical School yearbooks (includes one copy of the 1915 "Cadduceus"). The materials range in date from 1948-92.
  General
  There is as complete a set as the Univeristy Archives has in the Reading Room. There are duplicate copies in the following boxes.
  Box 1 has yearbooks dating 1949-1965 Box 2 has yearbooks dating 1966-1977 Box 3 has yearbooks dating 1981-1988
  - Caduceus, 1915 (Box 2)
    2 copies; one from former ACC#845
  - Speculum, 1948-1970 (Box 1, Box 2)
    A yearbook for 1951 is not among these yearbooks.
  - Synapse, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Washington Circle, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - The Labyrinth: GWU Medical School, 1976 (Box 2)
    1 ocpy
  - George Washington University Medical Yearbook, 1977 (Box 2)
    No yearbooks for 1978, 1980, 1982, 1986, 1990.
  - The George Washington University School of Medicine, 1979-1992 (Box 2, Box 3)
- Friday Report, 1970-1989; RG0007 Series 26; 1 Linear foot (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series consists of "Friday Report," the newsletter of the Medical Center Office of Public Relations, 1970-89
- GW Medicine and Health magazine, 1965-2016; RG0007 Series 27; 2.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5)
  This series consists of "GW Medicine and Health Magazine," a publication of the GW Medical Center Office of Public Relations. The materials range in date from 1965-2011.
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Bound volume
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Summer, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Winter 1981-82, Summer/Fall 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Winter/Spring, Summer/Fall, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Spring/Summer 1984, Fall/Winter 1984-85, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Spring/Summer 1985, Fall/Winter 1985-86, Spring/Summer 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Fall/Winter, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Spring/Summer 1987, Fall/Winter 1987-88, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Fall, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Spring and Fall, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Spring and Fall, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Spring, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Summer, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Winter, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Fall, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Winter, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Spring, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - GW Medicine and Health Magazine: Winter, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)